Ok.
So, now that I have the placket taken apart.
All the seams are undone.
This ninety degree angle that's already there has been taken apart.
And, this is what I want to show you how to work on next is this top placket piece.
And, we look underneath you can tell it's two angles put together to make a ninety degree.
Most of the time, it's forty-five and forty-five.
And, this one's a little bit off just because it's not as well made.
So, what we're going to do is take ours and just refold it right there at right there.
And, the idea is to make my three quarters of an inch chalk line to the original crease that's folded over on the placket.
This is ninety degrees and these two pieces on the side are forty-five degrees to make one-eighty.
So, you can tell this is a hundred and eighty degree angle right here.
And, to keep this I want to go ahead and just pin it.
Pin this right here and then I'm going to pin this one.
And, in the next clip I'm going to show you how to fold it over and we're going to have it pinned and folded before we even get an iron to it.
So, we'll do that in the next clip.